Product + UX Designer

Stefanie Mendoza

<u>Contact</u> Stefanievmendoza.com svm005@ucsd.edu

714.305.6250

Summary

A Product Designer who tackles complex problems by using her creativity, empathy, and curiosity to design impactful solutions. She has experience in conducting user research and visual design, taking ideas from concepts to prototypes that have received recognition and praise from mentors and stakeholders.

Skills

Tools: Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, Indesign, After Effects, Figma, Sketch

Design: User Interface, Sketching, Wire-framing, User Research, User Testing, Prototyping,

Paper Prototyping, A/B testing, Ethnographic Research

Development: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Java (basic), Python (basic), Git, Heroku

Education

University of California, San Diego 2017-2021 B.S: Speculative Design Minor: Cognitive Science w/ Specialization in Design & Interaction

UC, San Diego Extension 2019-2020 Front End Development Certification

Experience

Diabetes Design Initiative

Product Design Jan 2020 - Ongoing

Currently a project manager, conducting user research and design to reimagine diabetes education with DDI. We have Implemented a visualization data tool for people with diabetes around the world.

Dexcom

UX/UI Design Apr 2020 - Jun 2020

In collaboration with Dexcom designers to redesign the Dexcom Clarity website. Conducted user research, testing and developed prototypes for the Dexcom stakeholders.